luxuryrealestate.com 2005-12-31

# LuxuryRealEstate.com

LuxuryRealEstate.com  
Privacy Policy  
Updated 3/12/2004.

**BY PROVIDING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US ON THIS WEB SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF THAT INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

John Brian Losh, Inc., doing business as LuxuryRealEstate.com ("LuxuryRealEstate.com," "us," or "we"), respects the privacy concerns of visitors to the LuxuryRealEstate.com Web site. We are proud of our information practices, and we want you to know the steps we take to protect the personal information you may provide to us. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on this Web site and does not apply to any other Web site operated by a member of Who's Who in Luxury Real Estate.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We may modify, alter, or update this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this policy frequently. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on **July 24, 2003**.

**Information We Collect Automatically**  
If you merely browse through the LuxuryRealEstate.com Web site or download information, our servers will automatically collect certain information from you. This information includes the: (a) name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; (b) browser software you use and your operating system; and (c) Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to this Web site. We will use information that we automatically collect to manage and improve our Web site to make it as useful as possible for visitors like you. None of the information we automatically collect is tied to personal information you may provide to us.

**Information You Choose to Provide to Us**  
LuxuryRealEstate.com gathers and retains personal information about you only when voluntarily submitted by you. For example, if you choose to complete and submit one of the forms located on our Web site to order products, register for conferences, register to receive information, or join Who's Who in Luxury Real Estate, we will retain the information you submit to respond to your inquiry, consider your request or fill your order. After we have taken the appropriate action, the information you submitted will be retained for our records. If we change the manner we use or retain personal information you provide to us, we will update this Privacy Policy. 

If you choose to submit information on the "E-mail a Friend About This Property!" page, we will retain the information you provide to us on this form. LuxuryRealEstate.com will use the e-mail address of your friend to tell him or her of your referral and to provide the information about the property. The e-mail we send to your friend will allow that person to request that we remove their personal information from our system. We will not sell, rent, or otherwise disclose the information you provide on the "E-mail a Friend About This Property!" page to any person or entity except as stated in the "Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties" section of this Privacy Policy.

**Personal Information as an Asset of LuxuryRealEstate.com**  
The personal information you provide to us is an asset of LuxuryRealEstate.com. If LuxuryRealEstate.com or a substantial part of our business is sold or otherwise transferred to a third party, your personal information may be transferred as well. We will notify you of any transfer of your personal information in connection with such a major transaction. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties**  
Except for a major transaction as described above, LuxuryRealEstate.com will not sell or rent the personal information you provide to us to any third party without first obtaining your consent. In addition, we will not disclose the personal information you provide to us without your consent, except: (a) as required by law, (b) to our independent contractors who host and maintain our Web site and e-mail services; (c) to service providers or suppliers if the disclosure will enable that party to perform business, professional or technical support for us; and (d) to third party associates who may have products or services of interest to you.

**Opting Out of Receiving Promotional Materials**  
Unless you opt out of receiving promotional materials, we may send you information by e-mail or postal mail to the addresses you submit to us on the pages of our Web site. From time to time, we may send newsletters to you, notify you of special promotions, new products or services, or other information that may interest you. You may also receive notifications of special promotions, new products or services from our third party associates. 

If you do not want to receive promotional information from us or our third party associates, you will be able to express this preference by clicking on the appropriate button or checkbox provided on the screen at which you fill out on-line forms. If you do not want to receive promotional material from us or our third party associates and you did not indicate this preference when you sent personal information to us, you may use the "Contact Us" page to change your preference. Upon receipt of your request, we will take reasonable steps to deactivate your name from our marketing lists. 

**Cookies**  
A "cookie" is a small text file that a Web site can place on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping or other administrative purposes. We use cookies on this web site for the sole purpose of effective navigation through this site, www.luxuryrealestate.com, not for tracking users' browsing history

**Security**  
We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. You should be aware, however, that no transmission over the Internet, and no electronic data storage method, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of the personal information you provide to us either during its transmission or its storage on LuxuryRealEstate.com's systems. 

**Links to Other Web sites**  
LuxuryRealEstate.com does not endorse and is not responsible for the information practices or privacy policies of Web sites operated by others that may be linked to our Web site. If you decide to access a third party's Web site that may be linked to this Web site, you should consult that Web site's privacy policy. 

**Member's Web sites**  
Some members of Who's Who in Luxury Real Estate operate their own Web sites. Although some of these Web sites are hosted by us, and may even be designated as being "powered by LuxuryRealEstate.com" or "hosted by LuxuryRealEstate.com", these Web sites are operated by independent persons or entities that are not controlled by LuxuryRealEstate.com. Accordingly, we do not control or otherwise dictate the content or policies of such Web sites and do not require members to adhere to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Consequently, you should review the privacy policy of any member's Web site you may visit before providing personal information on that Web site.

**Children**  
It is not our intention to collect personal information from anyone under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you may use this Web site only with the involvement of an adult. 

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have questions about how we use the personal information you may provide us on this Web site or about this Privacy Policy, or would like to change or delete such information, please contact us using the information listed on our "Contact Us" page. For technical questions about the operation of this Web site, please contact us at [web@LuxuryRealEstate.com](mailto:web@LuxuryRealEstate.com).
